我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so I opened up our world to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
欢迎来到地球二
Welcome to Earth-2.
我见过你的二重身
I met your doppelganger.
她叫冰霜杀手  是冷酷无情的冰雪女魔
She's a cold-hearted ice queen named Killer Frost.
-我叫震波  -回波
- The name is Vibe. - Reverb.
我的兄弟姐妹们
My brothers and sisters,
我带我们进入了这个新世界
I've brought us to this new world,
供我们随意夺取
ours for the taking!
这是谁的世界
Whose world is this?
我们的世界
Our world!
装弹
Reloading!
大卫
David!
后门  队长受伤了
Back door! Captain's down.
走走走
Go, go, go, go, go!
趴下  快趴下
Down, down! Down, get down!
有些人称之为"超能末日"
Some people are calling it the Metapocalypse,
那一天  一支拥有超乎想像之能的军队
the days when Central City was overrun
在中城横行无忌
by an army with powers beyond imagination.
超能末日  城市遭受危机
但在这黑暗的时刻
But in these dark times,
我们绝不能忘记我们自己的力量
we must never forget our own strength,
我们回击的力量
our own power to fight back.
因为只有在至黑之夜中
That it is only in the blackest of nights
我们才能真正看到光明
that we can truly see the light...
并且真切地意识到我们并不孤独
and know for sure we are not alone.
我们从来  没有  孤独过
We are never...ever... alone.
咱们平常都是一个个干掉这些家伙
We usually take these guys down one at a time,
而不是一下一百个
not 100 at a time.
可你看上去完全没有被累到
And yet, you don't seem overwhelmed.
我知道我们能解决的
I know we can do it.
两位  你们得来看看这个
Guys. You have to come see this.
西斯科  你要干什...
Cisco, what are you...
凯特琳
Caitlin?
她受惊了
She's in shock.
有一些...脱水以及营养不良
A little... dehydrated and malnourished,
但我觉得她会没事的
but I think she'll be fine.
我没事
I'm okay.
发生了什么  你是怎么逃脱的
What happened? How did you get away?
他...放我走的
He... let me go.
我没想到他会放我走  我以为是个陷阱
I didn't think he would; I thought it was a trap.
但是  他告诉我你死了
But... he told me you were dead.
我没有  我就在这里呢
I'm not. I'm right here.
我们都在  在一起
We're all here, together.
斯诺
Snow.
杰伊不在这里  你很安全
Jay's not here. You're safe.
他会占领这座城市  你阻止不了他
He's gonna overrun the city. You can't stop him.
我们可以的
Yes, we can.
听我说  他不会得逞的
Listen to me, he's not going to succeed.
我们可以解决的  这是我们的地球
We've got this. This is our Earth.
你不能肯定  你不知道他有多强大
You don't know that. You don't know what he is capable of.
进入神速力之中让我了解到
I know from being in the Speed Force
宇宙是站在我们这一边的
that the universe is with us,
而不是极速那边
not Zoom.
如果宇宙和我们同在  我们怎么可能输
And if the universe is with us, how could we possibly lose?
对吗  各位
Right, guys?
对对  没错
Yeah, yeah, right.
你经历了太多事
You've been through a lot.
应该去休息下  来吧
You should get some rest, come on.
你进了神速力
You were in the Speed Force?
我...是你不在的时候
I...when you were gone.
一言难尽  不过我们想找回我的力量
It's hard to explain, but we tried to get my powers back
然后当黑暗物质闪电...
and when the dark matter lightning...
好吧  我就直说了
Okay, I'm gonna say it.
你们不觉得他有些太...
Um, we don't think he's being just a little too--
过度自信
Overconfident?
可能是他进了神速力的原因
Yeah, maybe it was his time in the Speed Force.
他现在表现的好像刀枪不入一般
I mean, he's acting like he's invincible now or something.
是啊  好像再也没有什么能令他困扰了
Yeah, like nothing fazes him anymore,
这可不...
which isn't--
现实  没错
Realistic, no.
应该有人和他谈谈  以免他放松警惕
Somebody needs to talk to him before letting his guard down
让自己受伤  或更糟
gets him hurt or worse.
他确实把我从昏迷中唤醒了
He did bring me out of my coma.
这肯定会让人有点飘飘欲仙
That's bound to make someone a little overly chipper.
就像我说的  得有人去和他谈谈
Well, like I said, somebody needs to talk to him.
水星实验室
太棒了  阿努潘
Amazing job, Anupam.
这种突破局限的思维方式
This is exactly the kind of groundbreaking thinking
正是我成立这间公司的目的
I built this company for.
干得好
Well done.
水星实验室
所有人  立刻撤离
Everyone, evacuate! Now!
快
Hurry!
她睡得还真快
She's out like a light, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
杰伊确实伤她很深
Jay really did a number on her.
他对我们
It's not like he
也没怎么手下留情
exactly used kid gloves on the rest of us.
她会没事的  她只是需要时间
She'll be okay. She just needs time.
而我们只需要将极速打倒
And for us to finally bring Zoom down.
我们会成功的
Which we will.
是啊  因为宇宙与我们同在  对吧
Yeah, because the universe is with us, right?
听着  老兄
Listen, man...
西斯科
Cisco?
你没事吧
Hey. You okay?
-你刚才震波了  -是啊
- You just vibe? - Yeah.
你看到了什么
What'd you see?
我看到一只鸟
I saw a bird.
是一只死鸟
Like, a dead bird.
水星实验室
Mercury Labs.
那里被攻击了
It's under attack.
好的
All right.
谢谢你  艾伦先生
Thank you, Mr. Allen.
我不蠢
I'm not stupid.
轰
Boom.
你是怎么知道的
So how did you know?
-你的真实身份吗  -是的
- Your real identity? - Yeah.
拜托  巴里  我可是个科学家
Come on, Barry, I'm a scientist.
观察力很敏锐的
We're paid to be perceptive.
况且只要这城市发生灾难
And you're always a little too well informed
你都会立马得到消息
when things go pear-shaped in this city.
但我可没见过您
But I don't believe we've ever met before.
我是克里斯蒂娜·麦吉博士
Dr. Christina McGee.
我是亨利·艾伦医生
Doctor Henry Allen.
我是巴里的父亲
I'm Barry's father.
好了  既然都互相认识了
Okay, now that the cat's out of the bag,
你有没有看到弄塌大楼的人到底是谁
did you happen to see who it was that cause your building to collapse?
我什么也没看到  一切都太突然了
I didn't see anything. It happened so fast.
也许监控录像会有记录
Maybe the security cameras caught something?
我们能调取录像吗
Can we access them?
水星实验室确实有防损毁储存器
Mercury Labs does have a Crash-Survivable Memory Unit.
那是什么
A what?
就是大楼的黑匣子
Virtually a black box for buildings.
它可以储存大楼倒塌前的全部监控录像
It will have stored all the security footage right up until the building collapsed.
很好  我去找到它
Okay, great, I'll go find it.
这肯定不是哪个超能力者随机作案
This wasn't some random meta-human.
以往每次水星实验室被当成袭击目标时
Whenever Mercury Labs has been targeted in the past
都有特定的原因
there's always been a specific reason.
没错  作案者一定有所企图
Yeah, someone's after something.
是的  这个人很有可能就是极速
Yes, and that someone is probably Zoom.
还有另一种可能性
There may be one more possibility.
几个月前  我看到哈里森·威尔斯
A few months ago, I saw Harrison Wells
从我的大楼里跑了出来
running out of my facility.
这话听起来可能荒唐  但我确定就是他
I know it sounds crazy, but I'm certain it was him.
今天的事会不会是他干的
Is there any way he could have anything to do with this?
几个月以前
A few months ago?
的确是我
Sure.
可今天的事
Now?
并不是我
No.
看来要向你解释很多事了  麦吉博士
Yeah, there are a few more things that we could catch you up on, Dr. McGee.
我的包
Hey, my purse!
那不是你的东西  混蛋
That ain't yours, punk.
你犯了个大错
Big mistake.
今天可不是你逞英雄的时候
You picked a bad time to play hero.
爸爸
Dad?
沃利
Wally.
你刚才在干什么
What the hell were you doing?
那家伙抢了好多人
That guy just jacked a bunch of people
我要抓住他
so I had to go after him.
你差点把小命丢了
You could have got yourself killed!
我只是不想让这些坏人无法无天地犯罪
I'm not just gonna let these guys get away with this.
我必须做点什么
I have to do something.
沃利  他们可不是普通罪犯
Wally, these are not just guys!
他们可都是超能力者
These are meta-humans!
这种事交给警察和闪电侠来处理
Leaves this to the cops and The Flash.
闪电侠分身乏术
The Flash can't be everywhere at once.
我必须尽我之力来帮忙
I--I have to do what I can to help.
我要让他看到  我值得被拯救
I have to show him I was worth being saved.
沃利...
Wally...
你是...值得的
You are...worth it.
真的吗
Really?
值得吗
Am I?
因为我还记得
'Cause last time I checked,
我对病危的母亲避而不见
I'm the guy who avoided his dying mother for weeks.
我让许多人蒙羞了
I'm the guy who shamed a bunch of other guys
还非法地偷走了他们的车
and illegally took their cars from them.
我害闪电侠失去了超能力
I'm the guy who caused The Flash to lose his powers
从而造成了这场"超能末日"
and start this whole damn "Metapocalypse" In the first place.
-沃利  -我还记得
- Wally-- - Last time I checked,
有很多事情需要我去弥补
I've a whole lot to make up for.
我也决定要去弥补
That's what I intend to do.
可恶
Damn it.
斯诺
Snow.
我不知道你在
I didn't know you were here.
你在干什么
What you doing?
杰西让我给她检查一下
Uh--Jesse asked me to run some tests
看看她的基因序列有没有变化
to see if her genetic structure had changed.
你为什么要斯诺博士...
Why did you ask Dr. Snow...
再次对你进行检测
to run tests on you again?
因为我接触过暗物质
Because I got hit with a dark matter, okay?
那肯定会对我有所影响的
I mean, that must have affected me somehow.
你不是超能力者
You're not a meta-human.
你只是个
What you are
年轻的女孩
is a young woman
拥有着超高的智商
with a genius-level IQ
可以助我们击败新一批的超能力者
that we could use in our fight against this new wave of meta-humans.
好吧  我懂了
Okay. All right, fine.
很好
Fine.
斯诺
Snow?
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
-是这个吗  -就是它
- Is this it? - That's the one.
很好  爸爸  麦吉博士  西斯科
All right, great. Dad, Dr. McGee, Cisco.
你们把它搞开看有没有什么发现
why don't you guys crack this open, see what you can find?
好的
Sure.
我们去找找看什么样的超能力者
We'll go see what kind of meta-human powers
能弄塌那样一栋大楼
can take down a building like that
以及要如何打败他
and how to stop it.
-好的  -这活不错
- Great. - Sounds like fun.
好了  我去看看乔那边是否需要帮助
All right, I'm gonna go see if Joe needs any help in the streets.
这里没问题吧
Everybody cool here?
任务很简单  对吧
Should be a piece of cake, right?
小拳王
Hey, slugger!
能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a minute?
能啊  怎么了
Yeah, sure. What's up?
我记得你说过  你在神速力之中的遭遇
Well, I know you said that what happened to you in the Speed Force
改变了你看待事情的方式
changed the way you see things,
可你好像却很乐观
but you seem very optimistic, you know,
鉴于现在有那么多超能力者在城里肆虐
with a lot of meta-humans running around tearing up the city.
怎么  你在神速力中看见了未来吗
What, did you see the future in there?
不  这次没有
No--um-- not this time.
没有...我...
No--I--look--
我在神速力中的所见
What I was shown in the Speed Force
改变的不仅仅是我的思想
didn't just change my mind,
而是让我焕然一新
it changed me.
我不知道  你看到我这么乐观
I don't know-- what you're seeing as optimism is,
头一次  我不再害怕了
for the first time, i'm just not afraid anymore.
太棒了  那
Great, that's--
但是
But...
你得明白还是要小心行事  好吗
You know you still have to be careful, right?
什么意思
What do you mean?
那么
Well...
我不  你为什么总是想
I don't--why are you trying to
把我努力奋斗取得的东西夺走
take something from me that I fought so hard to get to?
-巴里  我  -你  你不知道
- Barry! I-- - you--you don't know
我经历了怎样的一切  爸爸
everything that I've been through, Dad.
你回来没多久所以不知道
You haven't been here long enough to know.
我不是那个意思  对不起
I didn't mean-- I'm sorry.
我不知道为什么这么说
I don't know why I said that.
我想我懂了
I think I do.
没陪在你身边
Hadn't been around.
教你如何开车或带你去看校园
Teach you how to drive or take you to look at colleges.
但我尽了一切所能去了解你
But I've done everything in my power to know who you are.
巴里  我不想夺走你的东西
Barry, I don't want to take anything from you.
我相信你
I believe in you.
问题不是我不相信你
This isn't about my not believing in you.
我明白
I know that.
我没事的  好吗
And I'm fine. Okay?
谢谢  非常谢谢你
Thank you, thank you very much
这么担心我
for worrying about me.
我爱你
I love you.
但我没事的
But I'm fine.
走
Come on.
那是什么
What is that?
是中城警局
It's CCPD.
极速
Zoom.
巴里
Barry.
别去
Don't do it.
你知道吗  我从没看过
You know, I never saw
我妈妈被害时的现场照片
the crime photos of my mother's murder.
我猜我不需要
Well, I guess I didn't need to.
你消失的时候我是头排看客
I have a ringside seat while you got whisked away.
太脆弱了  我猜
Too delicate, I suppose.
毕竟你不是全息投影  对吗  闪电侠
Not just a hologram after all, are you, Flash?
真有意思
Interesting.
我知道你叫我上来不是为了逗乐好玩
I know you didn't call me up here just to banter.
我们做个了结吧
Let's finish this.
就现在
Right now.
其实我正是为逗乐而来
Actually, I did.
我来找你就是要告诉你不能一个个
I called you up here to tell you you can't keep running
追赶超能力者
from one meta to the next.
一圈又一圈
Around and around,
就像狗在追自己的尾巴
like a dog chasing its tail.
我会不惜一切代价阻止你
I'll do whatever it takes to stop you.
但愿这么做就够了
If only that were good enough.
因为事情是这样的
'Cause here's the thing.
我了解你
I know you.
我了解你  我知道是什么在拖你后腿
I know you, I know what's holding you back.
我和你
You and me...
我们真的就是同一类人
we're really just the same person.
是啊  你一直这么说
Yeah, you keep saying that,
但这并不能让谎话成真
but it's not gonna make it true.
你看  我们一样
You'll see. We are.
悲催的背景一样
Same tragic background.
奔跑的原因一样
Same reason for running.
变得更快更强的渴望也一样
Same desire to be the fastest, to be the best.
不同的地方呢
The difference?
你认为你的愤怒是肮脏的
You think your anger is dirty somehow.
你想当纯粹的英雄
You want to be seen as pure, the hero.
这样难道不累吗
Doesn't it get exhausting?
这样难道不累吗  巴里
Doesn't it get exhausting, Barry!
装成杰伊那个样子是很累的  相信我
It was exhausting playing Jay, believe me.
我并没有在装
I'm not pretending.
如果是我
Now if it were me,
我会毫不犹豫地让那栋楼倒塌
I'd let that building tumble without a second thought.
但是你
But you,
你绝对不会让那种事发生  对吗
you'll never let that happen, will you?
这就是为什么我能打败你  巴里
That's why I'm gonna beat you, Barry.
因为你总是要去做那个英雄
Because you always have to be the hero.
而当你忙着扮演乖巧小男孩的时候
And while you're playing the good little boy...
我早就胜券在握了
I'll be busy winning.
我们不能让急速再摧毁一栋建筑了
We can't let Zoom destroy another building.
我们得制服他
We need to take him down.
现在
Now.
一支超能力大军正在中城
How do you propose we do that
为非作歹  你觉得我们该怎么做
with an army of meta-humans laying waste to Central City?
在我的地球上都没法阻止极速
We couldn't stop Zoom on my Earth.
现在怎么就有办法阻止了
What makes us different?
我们是个团队
We're a team.
先对付超能力者  他们是他的护盾
We start with the meta-humans, they're his armor.
我们先制服他们  极速势力就大减
We take them down first, then Zoom's more vulnerable.
巴里  我们甚至不知道他有多少爪牙
Barry, we don't even know how many of his minions there are.
数量可能成百上千
There could be hundreds, a thousand.
而他们所有人  都拥有不同的超能力
And all of them, they're all working with different powers.
要把他们一一制服可能需要几周时间
It could take weeks to track them all down.
各位  我们等不了几周了
Guys, we don't have weeks.
所以我们现在要做的是
So what we need do to is
想办法把他们一网打尽
come up with a way to stop them all at once.
怎么做
How?
西斯科
Cisco,
你的护目镜  你的摄像仪
your goggles, your camera,
他们在地球二上不起作用  对吗
they didn't work on Earth-2, right?
是的  频率完全不同
Yeah, it was a whole different frequency.
而你击败时间亡灵的办法
And the way you took down the Time Wraiths,
是基于频率的
that was based on frequency.
哈特利的看家本领
Hartley's entire shtick...
我觉得我明白你的意思了
I think I'm smelling what you're stepping in.
-对  -所以基本上就是  我们制造
- Yeah. - So basically, we create some vibrational tech
能击败地球二超能力者的振动装置
that can take down the Earth-2 metas.
-基本上如此  -我明白了
- Basically. - Oh, I gotcha.
-我也是  -我来帮忙
- Me too. - I'll help.
-好的  -《中城时报》有消息我通知你
- Okay. - I'll let you know if I hear anything from CCPN.
-谢谢  -别客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
各位
You guys...
我们能成功
we got this.
巴里  我能和你聊一下吗
Barry, can I talk to you for a second?
行
Yeah.
鸟
Birds.
为什么
Why?
就像我脑子里演了一部希区柯克电影
It's like a Hitchcock movie in my head.
怎么了
What's up?
是沃利的事
Man, it's Wally.
他还好吧
Is he okay?
不太好
Not really.
早前  他认为用自己做诱饵
Earlier, he thought it would be a good idea
来对付超能力疯子
if he used himself
是个不错的主意
as bait against a meta-human psycho.
他认为自己能像闪电侠一样行事
Thought he could do things the way The Flash would.
乔  他的确和我说过
Joe, I mean, he-- he did tell me that
他不会浪费闪电侠赐予他的机会
he wasn't gonna waste the opportunity The Flash gave him.
我不知道你是否能阻止他
I don't know if you can stop him.
我必须阻止他  不然他会害死自己的
I'm gonna have to or he's gonna get himself killed.
他不是你  巴里
Look, he ain't you, Barry.
这只是句玩笑
He can't just go Mach 50--
一小时跑61155公里只是浮云
Mach 50 isn't a real thing.
问题是
The point is
认为自己所向披靡无法保护他
thinking you're invincible isn't any kind of armor.
沃利现在的危险度已经超出我能承受的范围
Wally's already at a higher risk than I'm comfortable with,
而他还把这些警告完全当作耳边风
and him throwing caution to the wind on top of all that?
不行
No.
我们要保证他的安全
We got to keep him safe.
所以用闪电侠的身份
So... in the Flash,
和他谈谈
talk to him.
再谈一次
Again.
好  我会尽量和他谈  我保证
Yeah, I'll talk to him. I'll try, I promise.
好
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
扔东西不是
I thought throwing things was
哈里最喜欢减轻压力的方法吗
Harry's preferred method of dealing with stress.
我现在非常地沮丧
That is how frustrated I am right now.
我怎么都想不出办法
I'm-- just running out of ideas
不知道该怎么解决这件事  巴里呢
as to how to make this work. Where's Barry?
我要尝试一下漫步阳光下的感觉
I need a taste of that "Walking on sunshine" thing
就像他现在在做的那样
he's got going on right now.
不不
No... no!
是我
It's me, okay?
深呼吸  深呼吸
Breathe. Breathe.
没事吧  你全身在颤抖
You're okay, all right? You're shaking.
我以为我看到了极速
I-- I thought I saw him-- Zoom--
我以为我看到他在这里
I thought I saw him right there.
这里只有我
It's just me, okay?
看着我  他不在这里
Look at me, he's not here.
他不在
He's not here.
我到处都能到他
I see him everywhere.
你刚刚
Look, you literally
才从绑架你的疯子手下逃脱  知道吗
just escaped a psychopath who kidnapped you, all right,
所以你有这样剧烈的反应
so I think it's normal for you to have
是很正常的
a severe reaction like this.
这次更严重
This is so much worse than that.
我一直都很害怕
I-- I'm afraid all the time.
我觉得我根本没法忘却这场经历
I don't think I can ever move forward.
你会的
You will.
什么时候
When?
杰伊夺走了我的一切
Jay took everything from me.
我的自信  信任以及心智
My confidence, my trust, my sanity.
我觉得我再也无法恢复了
I don't think I'll ever be whole again.
你当然会
Of course you will.
我保证
I promise.
收到  正在赶往  预计四分钟到达
Copy that. En route ETA in 4 minutes
请派支援去42街
and send backup at 42th.
偷东西是犯法的
Stealing is illegal, you know.
韦斯特警探跟我说
Detective West tells me that you've been
你单枪匹马对抗极速的军队
fighting Zoom's army on your own.
是的  我想帮忙
Yeah. I want to help.
我很钦佩你努力在做的事
I admire what you're trying to do,
但是最好的方法
but the best way to help is to just
就是交给警察来处理
leave this to the police.
就像你这样
Like you did.
我是有超能力的  沃利  这稍有些不同
I do have powers, Wally. It is a little different.
这不是你的战斗
This isn't your fight.
而是我的
It's mine.
不  是我们所有人的战斗
No, it's all of ours.
现在这里也是我的城市
This is my city too now.
由我们所有的人一起来保护它
It's up to all of us to protect it.
巴里  我们收到重大的超能力者警报
Barry, we got a major meta-human alert
在第五街和主街交界处  快赶过去
at 5th and Main-- get there.
第五街和主街交界处  收到
5th and Main. Got it.
我们晚点再聊
We'll continue this later.
为什么总是如此难以抉择
Why is it always so difficult to choose?
巴里  是什么事
Barry, what it is?
是
It's--
劳蕾尔·兰斯
Laurel Lance.
劳蕾尔
Laurel.
劳蕾尔·兰斯已经死了
Laurel Lance is dead.
至少在这地球上是
On this Earth, anyway.
可怜的黑金丝雀  拜拜小鸟儿
Poor Black Canary. Bye-bye, birdy.
地球二的劳蕾尔
Earth-2 Laurel.
你认识她的二重身吗
You knew her doppelganger?
我们不止认识她  我们还很爱她
We didn't just know her, we loved her.
那我该怎么称呼你呢
So... what do I call you?
你可以叫我
You can call me
黑海妖
Black Siren.
极速说过你也许会出现
Zoom mentioned that you might be showing up.
如果他和你说了我的能力
If he told you what I can do,
你应该更害怕我才对
you should look more afraid.
你也应该害怕我
And so should you.
告诉我
Tell me,
你为什么要摧毁水星实验室
why did you take down Mercury Labs?
因为我喜欢看着东西分崩离析
Because I like to watch things crumble and fall.
你猜怎么着  下一个就轮到你  小红
Guess what. You're next, red.
你没事吧  巴里
You okay, Barry?
超过两百分贝的声音地人类是致命的
Look. Anything over 200 decibels will kill a human.
太大声了吗
Was that too loud?
也许我们应该把声音降下来
Perhaps we should quiet things down a bit.
令人难过的是
You know, the sad thing is,
我认为极速其实很怕你
I think Zoom's actually afraid of you.
以前我认为他无所畏惧
And I didn't think that he feared anything.
而你  你毫不令人心惊胆战
And you, you're hardly worth the chills.
他派了多少超能力者来杀你
How many metas did he send to try and kill you?
太可惜了
Well, it's too bad.
他早就应该派我来
He should have just sent me because that way,
这样你早就可以...
you would have already been--
上车
Get in.
我想你应该需要人接送
Thought you might need a lift.
是的  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
为什么那么多和我们作对的坏人
Why do so many villains that we go against
都用声波做武器呢
use sound as a weapon?
-什么  -没什么
- What? - Nothing.
-你没事了  -多谢
- You're gonna be fine. - Thanks.
沃利在你们激战的时候刚好路过吗
So Wally just drove on up into the thick of it?
你俩一定是谈过话
Must have been some conversation you two had,
他的做法和我们的意愿完全相悖
seeing as though he did literally the opposite of what we wanted.
这回我能听到了
This I can hear.
这不好笑
It's not funny.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我没心情开玩笑
I'm in no laughing mood.
乔  我试过了
Look, Joe, I tried.
我告诉过你会试试的
I told you I would try, right?
沃利是个坚定的人
Wally's a determined kid.
是啊  坚定地自寻死路
Yeah, determined to get himself killed.
坚定地想帮助别人  你应该高兴
Or determined to help people, and be glad or you know,
不然我就不能站在这里了
I would not be standing here right now.
那是他今晚走运
Well he was lucky tonight.
我不想看到他不走运的时候
I don't want to see the day when he isn't.
我们有的不只是幸运  乔
We've got more than luck on our side, Joe.
你知道自己不是无敌的  对吗
You know you're not invincible, right?
是的  我当然知道
Yes, of course, I know this.
乔有点保护过度  但是我懂
Joe's being overprotective, but I get it.
可你似乎觉得
Yeah, but it's like
没什么东西能触碰到你
you think that nothing can touch you.
你不会遇到不好的事物
Like nothing bad can get in your way.
对我们每个人来说  这都不是真的
That's not true for any of us.
什么意思
What are you saying?
我知道你在神速力中获取了经验
Look, I know that you had an experience in the Speed Force.
我也很高兴你确定我们会胜利
And I'm happy that you think we're gonna win the day.
但是有一丝恐惧是好事
But I think a little fear can be a healthy thing.
这能帮你选择该不该冒险
It helps you determine which risks are worth taking.
我希望你和沃利
I think that's something for both
都能铭记这一点
you and Wally to take to heart.
今晚我见到了你的红衣服朋友
I met your little red friend tonight.
不想问我有没有杀了他吗
Aren't you going to ask me if I killed him?
你没有
You didn't.
你很优秀  但还不够优秀
You're good but not that good.
可我是你左膀右臂中
And yet I seem to be
唯一还活着的人
the only one of your top lieutenants still standing.
我说了  你很优秀
Like I said, you're good.
为什么不再多摧毁几栋楼
So why don't you go knock down a few more buildings?
按我的要求
Like I ordered.
这样做意义在哪里
What's the point?
意义就是  让一切看起来很随机
The point is so that it seems random.
这样闪电侠和他的帮手们
That way The Flash and his merry band won't
就不能及时发现我的真正意图
realize what I'm up to till it's too late.
你的意图是什么
What are you up to?
世界毁灭
No good.
抱歉
Sorry.
好了
There we go.
你是在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me with this?
至少这个有用
Hey, at least it works.
太可怕了
Tremendous.
这到底是什么
What is it exactly?
就是个小玩意儿
It's just a small source of joy,
但重要的是  它能帮我们打败极速的军队
but more importantly, it's how we're gonna stop Zoom's army.
都给他们进行电击治疗吗
By giving them all electroshock therapy?
把他们全都用脉冲震晕
By giving them all dimensional shock therapy.
你又开始对牛弹琴了
This is where I play stupid and you explain science.
好吧  说得对
Okay. Fair enough.
所有事物都有特定的自振频率  对吧
So all matter vibrates at its own unique frequency, right?
打破这个频率  它就毁了
You disrupt that frequency, you disrupt the matter.
就像高音歌手能唱碎杯子
Like how an opera singer shatters glass with her voice.
没错  我们发现
Exactly. So we found out that
来自地球二的人  都有特定的
all Earth-2 people vibrate at their own,
-更不规律的自振频率  -更高频
- more erratic frequency. - Higher frequency.
-不同的频率  -高频
- Different frequency. - Higher.
-比我们的频率更高  -对
- Higher frequency than we do. - Right.
于是我去问了哈特利
So I ran this all past Hartley, right?
他建议我们
And he postulated that we could create
可以制作一个激波音叉  那就是
a sort of dimensional tuning fork-- voila--
这不是你一个人的功劳
Okay, you didn't do it yourself.
让我说完  可以吗
Just let me have this one, okay?
-继续  继续  -谢谢
- Have it, have it. - Thank you.
如果你绕着城市跑得足够快
So if you run around the city
就可以形成一个折射场
fast enough to create a refracting field,
这个装置发出的脉冲
the device can send out a pulse
就会反弹  分解
that'll bounce off of it, split apart,
然后不停地相互撞击
and collide with itself over and over.
放大脉冲对地球二生物不规律频率...
Amplifying it to an erratic frequency on the Earth-2...
-更高  更高频  -更高频
- Higher. Higher frequency. - Higher frequency
...的影响
...on the Earth-2 spectrum.
当脉冲冲击到地球二上的人
And when that pulse hits anyone from Earth-2--
就会击溃他们的神经系统
It'll disrupt their nervous system.
地球二的超能力者就睡着了
Earth-2 metas go night-night.
-包括极速吗  -包括极速
- Even Zoom? - Even Zoom.
哈里和杰西也来自地球二
Harry and Jesse are from Earth-2.
怎么能让脉冲不伤害到他们
How do we keep the pulse from hurting them?
警探  没想到你还关心这个
Oh, Detective, I didn't know you cared.
你知道我关心
Yes you did.
我们设计了这个耳机
Uh, we designed these headphones
来抵御脉冲
to protect us from the pulse.
威尔斯牌耳机
Beats by Wells.
发现黑海妖
西斯科  你的超能力者警报程序
Cisco, it's your meta-human alert app.
那里是西部高层区
That's the high-rise development on the west side.
那里住着好几百人
Hundreds of people live there.
拉蒙  到我们了  开始吧
Ramon, we're up. Let's go.
现在就发射脉冲
Set that pulse off right now.
艾伦  你现在就去跑出反射场
Allen you need to start generating that refracting field right now.
可黑海妖随时会摧毁这栋楼
But Black Siren can take down this building at any point.
有那么多人  威尔斯
Wha--all those people, Wells.
我们等着的时候  会死多少人
How many more people are gonna die while we wait?
各位  到底怎么办
Guys, which is it?
我总是能想到最糟的主意
I think I just got the worst idea of all time.
似乎从没一次摧毁过这么多栋楼
I don't think I've taken down so many buildings at once.
或许你没有自己想像中的强大
Maybe you're not as powerful as you think!
你们俩怎么在这儿
What are you two doing here?
怎么能让你一人享受乐趣呢
Why should you have all the fun?
我以为你们两个死了
I thought you two were dead.
极速也是这么以为的
Zoom thinks that too.
我们还想就让他这么以为吧
And we'd like to keep it that way.
暂且这样
For now.
你觉得你们两个能骗过极速吗
You think you two can pull one over on Zoom?
那你们就扮死人扮个痛快吧
Well, enjoy being dead.
我说过的
I told you.
给她个机会
Give her a chance.
什么机会
What chance?
她还没准备好
She's not ready.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你们知道我能做什么吗
Do you know what I'm capable of doing?
放马过来  我不费吹灰之力
Try it, and I'll shatter your entire
就能粉碎你的整个神经系统
nervous system without breaking a sweat.
你还真以为你能和极速较量
Wow, you really think you can take on Zoom.
我们可以
We can.
你根本不知道你自己有多强大
You don't even know how powerful you are.
发出一阵声波就可以拆掉一栋建筑
With a single call, you can take down a building.
真是叹为观止
I'd call that impressive.
但是为何就此
But why...stop...
止步不前
there?
若你可以成为主宰  成为神
Why serve a master when you can be a master,
为何要侍奉别人
when you can be a God?
我们  可以成为神
We...could be Gods.
-好了吗  -好啦
- All right? - All right.
不管那玩意是什么  我们同步上了
We're synced up with whatever the heck that thing is.
终于有东西我不懂你也不懂了
Finally something we're both baffled by.
我开玩笑的  那个
I'm kidding. That, my friend,
是75KTSB 4万瓦特的回响声波放大器
is a 75KTSB 40,000-watt reverberating sound amplifier
可以筛选出这个星球上
designed to single out the operating frequency
所有地球二生物的输出频率
of every single Earth-2 being on this planet--
由闪电侠控制和放大
which, went contained and magnified
创造出环绕整个城市的声波墙
by the Flash creating a sound pressure wall around the city,
使得所有地球二生物失去知觉
will render all of us earth-2 beings unconscious.
这样一来
Hence...
就有了安全保障措施
the safety precautions.
我已经晕了
I'm baffled by it.
准备好了吗
Are we ready?
准备好了
Yes, we are.
好的
All right.
好戏上演了
Here...we... go.
如果我有兴趣和你们两个结盟
If I were interested in forming an alliance with you two,
你们究竟有什么计划
what's your plan, exactly?
我们在中城警局伏击极速
We ambush Zoom at CCPD.
有了我们三个人的力量
With our three powers combined,
他不会是我们的对手
he'll be no match for us.
这听起来不错
Well, I like the sound of that.
很好
Great.
那我们出发吧
Then let's go.
还剩一件事
There's just one more thing.
回波  接住了
Reverb...catch.
你知道  所有的二重身
You know, all doppelgangers--
他们都是自己镜像
they're mirror images of themselves.
但你们两个  你们不知道对不
But you two, you didn't know that, did you?
回波是左撇子
Reverb is left-handed.
我只是  我不经意间
Well, I just-- I just happened to--
用右手接住了  快跑
catch it with my right-- run!
糟了
Oh, no.
我们怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我觉得你们没什么能办的
I don't think that there's anything you can do.
这是什么鬼
What the what?
我不知道
I don't know.
再来一遍啊
Well, do it again!
西斯科
Cisco...
可以了
We're a go.
在这个地球上没有任何东西
There's nothing on this Earth
能阻止我们
that can stop us!
有用了
It's working.
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸  好难受
Dad, it hurts.
-不不  不要  -没事的
- No--no--stop-- - It's okay.
-不  -没事的  宝贝
- No... - It's okay, honey.
快关掉  快关掉  有效了
Turn it off! Turn it off, it worked!
没事了  我们会照顾好他的
It's okay, it's okay, we'll take care of him.
没事的  杰西
It's okay, Jesse.
他会没事的
He's gonna be okay.
巴里  我们成功了
Barry. We did it.
把他们都抓起来
Bring them all in.
收到  我去收场
Copy that. I'm on clean up.
你说什么  我听不见
What's that? I can't--I can't hear you
这有双层隔音玻璃
through the double-paned soundproof glass.
要理解你在说什么有点难哦
It's--it's kind of hard to make out what you're saying.
我们要告诉莎拉和兰斯队长她的事吗
So should we tell Sara and Captain Lance about her?
不  我见识过和自己家人的
No, I've seen what interacting with
二重身有交集是什么后果
your family's doppelgangers can do.
她根本不是劳蕾尔
It's not even Laurel.
不  这只是个可悲的模仿品
No. It's just a poor imitation.
说起来  你刚才演
Speaking of, that was a pretty good
冰霜杀手还真像
Killer Frost you did back there.
可能我刚才正好有感觉
Guess I was in the right head space
扮演冰冷邪恶的杀手
to play a cold, vicious killer.
你怎么样  你还好吗
How you doing, are you okay?
不怎么样
No.
但我会没事的
But I think I'm gonna be.
和你们在一起
Being out there with you guys,
同超能力者抗争
fighting meta-humans,
拯救生命
saving people...
是这么久以来
It's the first time I felt
我第一次感到恢复正常
normal in a long time.
来抱抱
Come here.
-现在是集体抱抱的时候  -是啊
- This is a group hug moment. - Yeah. It is.
中城警局
所有极速带来的超能力者
So all of Zoom's meta-humans
都关在铁山监狱了吗
are locked up in Iron Heights?
一部分是的  一些在其他地方
Most of them. Some are somewhere else.
我不想知道细节
I don't want to know.
你不会想知道的
No you don't.
极速呢
And Zoom?
我们审讯的超能力者说
The metas we spoke to said Zoom
极速制造了一个缺口逃跑了
created a breach and escaped.
他怎么做到的
And how did he do that again?
谁知道  但他现在回地球二了
Who knows, but he's back on Earth-2 now.
地球二
Earth-2?
这又是我不想知道的事情吗
That something else I don't want to know about?
是的
No.
那好吧  闪电侠  谢谢
All right. Well, Flash, thanks.
你再次拯救了中城
The man who saved Central City once again.
不  我们都属于同一支队伍
No, we're all just part of the same team.
说到队伍  艾伦到底在哪儿
Speaking of teams, where the hell is Allen?
抱歉  哥们  抱歉
Ooh--sorry, man, sorry--hey.
听见有人提我的名字  什么事
Heard my name. Uh, what's up?
很好  有大概一百份超能力犯罪案件
Good, well, you've got about 100 meta criminal cases
等着你看  如果我是你  我会立即开工
to get through, so I would get to cracking if I were you.
我这就开始
I will get right on that.
队长
Captain.
-干的漂亮  -谢谢
- Well done. - Thanks.
听着
Listen, uh,
我又想了想沃利的事
I've been thinking about Wally some more.
你准备再和他谈谈吗
Are you gonna talk to him again?
不  我不准备
No, I'm not.
为什么不
Why not?
因为他是你的儿子  乔
Because he's your son, Joe.
我知道他是我的儿子
I know he's my son.
我  听着  我想说他继承了你的价值观
I--look--what I mean is he's got your values.
他继承了你想帮助别人走正道的内驱力
He's got your inner drive to help people do what's right.
我们应该向超越自己的理想看齐
We're supposed to think we're something we're not
直到目标实现
until we become that thing.
沃利就走在这条路上
That's the path that Wally's on.
我不会阻止他成为
I'm not gonna stop him from being the hero
那个他会成为的英雄
that he's gonna become.
我真的觉得你也不该插手
I really don't think you should either.
我真等不及到你有孩子折磨你的时候
I can't wait till you have kids and they torture you.
我会呵呵你一脸
I'ma laugh in your face.
好吧  老祖父
All right, gramps.
爷爷
Poppa.
啥
What?
我的孙子会叫我"爷爷"
My grandkids are gonna call me "Poppa".
好吧
All right.
这什么情况
What in the world?
这是什么
What is this?
-都怪爱瑞丝  -好吧
- Blame Iris. - Okay.
我只是觉得既然亨利正式回归了
I just figured that since Henry is officially back for good,
我们应该庆祝一下
we should celebrate.
而且极速离开了  城里现在也太平了
And since Zoom is gone and the city is quiet right now.
我很感激  爱瑞丝
Oh, I appreciate it, Iris.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-嗨  蒂娜  -你好  亨利
- Hi, Tina. - Hello, Henry.
杰西
Jesse.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你
Good to see you too.
你看上去  棒极了
You look...great.
谢谢
Thank you.
我希望你别介意我邀请了麦吉博士
I hope you don't mind that I invited Dr. McGee.
看起来某人很高兴你邀请了她
Seems like somebody's glad you did.
所以我猜你确实是战无不胜
So I guess you are invincible.
早就告诉你啦
Told you.
神速力与我们同在
The Speed Force is with us.
鉴于我
Since I'm
最近感到格外的战无不胜
feeling extra invincible lately,
你觉得如果
what do you say
你和我
you and I
再给彼此一次机会怎么样
give this a shot?
好  我很希望这样
Yeah, I would like that.
所以  是真的吗
So is it true?
你救了闪电侠一命
You saved The Flash's life?
我是说
Oh, I mean,
我只是在对的时间出现在对的地方罢了
I was just in the right place at the right time.
我为你骄傲  沃利
Proud of you, Wally.
你做的很好
You did good.
谢谢  爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
怎么了
What?
我只是  我也很为你骄傲
I'm just-- I'm proud of you too.
汤来了
Soup's on.
消灭一个充满怪物的城市
Taking out a city full of monsters
让人饥肠辘辘
makes a man hungry.
首先
First,
祝一杯酒
a toast.
敬家人
To family.
我就喜欢这样的祝酒词  简短又温馨
That's my kind of toast, short and sweet.
咱们开动吧
Let's eat.
又是你们  真棒
You guys. Great.
地球二
Earth-2.
西斯科
Cisco?
怎  怎么了
What--what is it?
你看到了什么
What'd you see?
你说看见是什么意思
What do you mean "See"?
西斯科有预见能力
Cisco gets visions.
我不明白
I don't understand.
明白什么  西斯科
What Cisco?
地球2号裂成了两半
Earth-2 splitting in half.
从北极裂到南极
Straight down to the poles.
告诉我  我没有感应到未来
Tell me I didn't just vibe the future.
请告诉我  我刚才没有看到世界末日
Please tell me I did not just see the end of the world!
我们的故事还在继续  闪电侠
Our story continues, Flash.
-亨利  -我的天呐
- Henry! - Oh, my God.
爸爸
Dad?
多有诗意啊  重回你童年的家
It's poetic, returning to your childhood home.
杰伊
Jay.
别这么做
Don't do this.
我求你了
I'm begging you.
求你了  冲着我来
I'm begging you! Take me.
-杀我吧  -不
- Kill me! - No!
你还是不肯相信我们是一样的
You still won't believe me that you and I are the same.
-别这样  -巴里  看着我  孩子
- Come on. - Barry, look at me, son.
所以我得逼你信我
So I'm gonna have to make you believe me.
不管发生什么  你都让我
Whatever happens, you have made me
-成为最幸福的父亲  -爸爸
- the happiest father... - Dad--
这次  你会看着你的父亲死去
This time, you're gonna watch your parent die
就像我一样
just like I did.
-不  别  -而这会让你变得
- No, no! - And this is what's gonna make you
和我一样
just like me!
-你妈妈和我爱  -杰伊
- Your mother and I love-- - Jay!
不
No!